

Aniket Bada Panda

CSE Undergrad Student '24

I am a second year student pursuing Computer Science Engineering with Specialization in Software Engineering @ SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Chennai. I am a Coder, a Freelance Video Editor, a business enthusiast and am more inclined towards conversations around startups and entrepreneurship. I love the field of digital marketing and data analytics and have worked for various clubs in my institution. I enjoy challenges that enable me to grow. I like to find application in what is taught to me and learn as quickly as possible.



aniketpanda1810@gmail.com



7738866493



www.hackerrank.com/aniket panda1810



linkedin.com/in/aniket-badapanda-2355221b8



github.com/aniketpanda18

EDUCATION

Btech in Computer Science and Engineering (Software Engineering)SRM Institute of Science and Technology, Kattankulathur

09/2020 - Present

CGPA

Semester 1 - 9.45

Semester 2 - 9.46

12th

Jaipuriar School, Sanpada

06/2018 - 07/2020

CBSE

75.4%

SKILLS

HTML

CSS



C++

PYTHON

Digital Marketing

Google Analytics

Video Editina

5 Star C++ HackerRank

WORK EXPERIENCE

Machine Learning Intern Internship Studio

02/2022 - Present Pune, India

Probable Committee Head

Aaruush National level Techno-management Fest

08/2021 - Present SRM University, Chennai

Marketing Committee Member SRM Indian Energy Conference

08/2021 - 12/2021 SRM University, Chennai

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi

Full Professional Proficiency

Oriva

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Machine Learning

Web Development

Blockchain

CERTIFICATES

Google Digital Garage (05/2021 - Present)

Digital Marketing

Google Analytics Academy (05/2021 - 05/2024)

SRM C Programming (07/2021 - Present)

300 Questions Solved

Python and Cyber Security (06/2021 - Present)

Developer Student Clubs (BIT Mesra)

Cloud Computing with AWS (11/2021 - Present)

Microsoft Learn Student Ambassador and GDG Ranchi

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Hospital Management System using Star UML (01/2022 - Present)